RINRIN (20)
HOSTESS
Why are you so condescending?
Because you're not being consistent.
MIMI (29)
HOSTESS
It's not like I'm here
to be educated by you, Mimi.
I'm saying you're free not to be.
I'm just saying--
I still don't know
why you're being condescending.
I'm just saying, you won't be liked.
- I don't care if they like me or not.
- Then you should go home.
That doesn't matter.
It's not like I'm here to be liked.
You should make an effort to be liked.
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
I think it's good to speak your mind.
It's good to have it out.
I just felt that what you were saying
didn't match what you were doing.
- Huh?
- Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt.
Huh?
What?
KAMAKEN (30)
MMA FIGHTER/BUSINESS OWNER
I screwed up today, so I just wanted
to apologize to everyone.
- I'm sorry.
- You're good.
- It's fine.
- Sorry I did that.
That's admirable.
- He's great when he's calm.
- He really is.
- That's what makes him scary.
- You're totally right.
- Why are you apologizing?
- Yeah.
Well, we had a pretty good vibe going on,
but then I… well, you…
you all had to step in.
Well, of course, we're a team.
- Thank you, guys.
- Mmm.
I'm glad you didn't get
expelled or suspended.
Hey, Mimi, you really stuck by me
and tried to calm me down.
So…
could I talk to you outside
for a little bit?
Oh, okay.
Seriously, if you hadn't been there today,
I don't know what would've happened.
So, yeah, I'm actually really grateful.
Thank you.
You had a terrifying look on your face.
You tried to stop me anyway.
Why did you do that?
Uh, because you shouted,
"I don't care if I get expelled!"
And I was like, "No,
it's too soon for that. Way too soon."
- Thank you.
- Like, it's only been one day.
Yeah, I don't want to get expelled.
Now that I've cooled off, I don't want to.
But I think you really took notice
of the fact that I was there,
and you listened to me
and paid attention to me.
I mean, it'd be pretty lame to go
fight again after what you did for me.
I feel like
I really owe you a lot for today.
No, I was glad to do it.
If I hadn't stopped you,
would you have stopped yourself?
Could you, if no one had stepped in?
I probably would've just waited
for an opportunity to punch him.
- You didn't stop.
- Hmm.
Yeah, so you were the only one
who stopped me and tried to calm me down.
- Well, I'm really grateful for that.
- I'm glad I stepped in when I did.
But because of what happened,
I feel like I want to get
to know you better and talk to you more.
So, I guess,
for the one-on-one conversations,
even though you're already taken,
I wanna ask you
to come talk to me after you're done.
Mmm.
So, I think I'm gonna try harder.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
IN OKINAWA
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
KITASHINCHI'S NO.1 HOSTESS
BLEEDING BIG-SIS ENERGY
MIMI
STRAIGHT-SHOOTING FORMER MMA CHAMP
KAMAKEN
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
Good morning.
It's time for Ethics class.
Life can only begin when you stop
running away from your past.
You will now reflect
on the mistakes you have made
and discuss them amongst yourselves.
Listen to other people's failures
and regrets,
so you can learn from them
by comparing them to yours.
For today's class, Mimi,
- you will be going first.
- Do I sit there?
Well, thanks for having me.
- Hey, you've got this.
- It's our pleasure.
I guess, my family
has always been kind of complicated.
And, well…
Okay, so, I moved around a lot,
so it was hard for me to fit in at school.
Like, in my first and second years
of junior high,
I was always getting
into fights and stuff like that.
Sometimes, the teachers wouldn't even
let me come into the classroom,
and so I couldn't keep up
with all the schoolwork.
KAZUMA (26) - SARA (26)
And my home environment
was just really, really bad.
So, I couldn't get along with my mom.
And between me and my third stepdad,
things just never got any better.
And in ninth grade,
I think it was right before the exams
to get into high school, in the winter,
I ran away from home.
After that, I started hanging out with
older people who were kind of difficult.
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
Then I started working at a girls' bar,
still in ninth grade.
I was kind of just living day to day.
And I went through
some pretty scary situations.
One time, I even nearly got dragged
into what could have been a sex crime.
There were days
when I honestly had nothing to eat,
and I didn't know if I'd be able to bathe.
So, yeah, I lived like that
for two or three months.
And when I didn't know what to do anymore,
that was when I ended up
being placed in a children's home.
So I got put in this children's home,
but I just couldn't fit in.
And my mom would come visit me there,
and she would say things like,
"I want you to come back home so much."
But the thing is, in my heart…
…I just didn't want to go back home,
and I also wanted to get away from my mom.
But I also didn't want
to give up on my future, you know?
RUNE (28)
RAPPER/BUSINESS OWNER
I always thought,
if I didn't have a high school diploma,
I wouldn't be able to do
what I wanted in life.
Then, it was totally random, but…
somebody suggested
that I try going to a cram school.
And I was excited, 'cause I'd never done
an after-school activity,
and I've always liked meeting people
outside my circle.
So I decided to go to the cram school.
And that was the first time
a teacher really understood
that I wasn't ready to listen to anyone,
and they taught me
at a pace that worked for me.
Yeah, this amazing teacher did that.
It was really incredible.
The class was, like, two hours long,
but I actually only ever studied
for ten minutes.
- Oh, really?
- But I'd get praise for having studied.
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
This teacher would talk to me
for the rest of the class.
Back then, I thought studying
was, like, super uncool.
I get it.
I thought listening to people was uncool.
But in the end, if there's anything
you want to do in life,
you have to study for it.
You even have to study
for a driver's license.
I hated anything that tried
to pigeonhole me when I was a kid.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
They made assumptions about me.
And I mean, usually…
usually they were right,
but sometimes they were wrong, you know?
- They'd always assume I'd done something.
- Yeah.
- They stereotyped you.
- Mmm-hmm.
I also experienced that at school,
where people blamed me
for things I didn't do.
- Yeah.
- Like, "I bet it was him again."
Even though it wasn't.
And after all of that,
I ended up punching the principal.
You crossed the line.
Next thing I knew,
I was in the principal's office,
and I was in handcuffs.
And then, I couldn't go to school anymore,
so that's something I really remember.
Like, I wanted to go to school,
but, at the same time, I couldn't.
And part of me thought
it would be lame if I went there,
made friends, and just sat there in class,
actually listening.
Yeah, I get what you're saying.
Yeah, so I totally understand
what you're saying.
- I get it too. For sure.
- Yeah.
Like, it felt kind of cool
to be a rebel, you know.
We all know.
It made you cool
if you didn't follow the rules.
- I just wanted to do things my way.
- All of us here were yankii, for sure.
- Yeah. Exactly.
- We've all been through that.
I thought it was just me
who thought like that.
- We all did.
- Guess I was wrong.
Now we know how lame we were.
Turns out we were the lame ones.
But that was the first time that
I met someone who actually understood me,
and without that teacher,
I don't think I would've been able to, uh…
Like, I'm still not mature enough,
but without them,
I probably wouldn't have been able
to do even the most basic shit
you're supposed to do as an adult.
- That was really nice.
- Sweet.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
So, we've heard Mimi
share her story during Ethics class.
You know,
I'm kind of similar to all of them.
Like, I was a pretty bad kid.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Is that so?
Well, he seems
to have become a pretty decent…
- Yeah, he's great now.
- …reliable person.
Yeah, I think I managed
to straighten myself out,
but my family situation was unusual…
Mmm.
…so I'm not sure if I can speak
for these participants here.
Some of my elementary
and junior high school teachers…
- Uh-huh.
- …were really supportive of me.
Even when I dropped out of school,
they were supportive.
Actually, I'd run away from home.
- Oh, dear.
- I was staying at my grandma's place.
And there was this teacher
who drove all the way to my grandma's,
and I'm still
just really grateful for that.
- Wow.
- Amazing.
Kids grow up
in all different kinds of environments,
and sometimes, they're dealing
with so many things on the inside.
That's true.
It's important to understand
their feelings and accept them.
'Cause life isn't easy,
and everybody's different.
So things might be a little bit hard
when you're a kid.
Having teachers like yours and hers
can dramatically change
the course of your life.
- Right.
- Meeting someone like that is important.
- Mimi was saved by that. That's so great.
- Right.
- What about you, Nagano?
- I don't know what to say.
- No?
- I said on live TV recently
that I don't feel like
any teachers helped me.
What?
There must be one.
Then I did my dance,
but it didn't go down well.
I bet it didn't.
The women will now have
a showdown to compete for a date.
- For real?
- It's the girls this time.
You will play a game of musical chairs.
They gonna throw punches?
You will walk around the circle
while the music is playing.
When the music stops,
you must sit on a stool.
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
If you don't sit on a stool,
you'll be eliminated.
MARU (28)
HOST/PRESIDENT
The last person left sitting on a stool
is the winner.
- I'm so gonna win.
- Yeah!
- Yeah?
- Hell, yeah.
Okay.
- Start?
- Do your best.
- Girls, spread out more.
- From here?
- On the count of three, start the music!
- Start the music!
- Oh, the music's cute.
- Go.
Wait, I'm scared.
- You can do it.
- Go on.
Look at that.
I can't tell when it's gonna stop.
You can do it!
- I'm scared.
- It's coming.
Stop it.
- Sara wins!
- Sara won that, Sara won that!
- Who won?
- What? Who won?
- Sara.
- The last person on the stool wins.
- Yeah.
- You did your best.
- So we take one stool out.
- It's so hot.
Okay, let's go.
- You did sit first.
- Don't feel bad.
- You sat first.
- You tried hard.
- No.
- You just got overpowered.
Boys can't even see properly.
- Shall we go?
- Just go for it.
All right, start the music!
- Here we go!
- I'm tired.
- It's faster this time.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- You're right.
Do we go faster?
- Man, I'm so nervous.
- Come on, girls.
It's making me nervous.
- Oh, careful!
- Go!
- Go, go, go!
- Go for it! Go for it!
Your arms are so long!
Did y'all see that?
She just reached for the chair
and grabbed it. You're so strong.
Sharan, are you okay?
- You went down hard.
- You okay?
- Good job.
- Poor girl.
You tried your hardest.
Okay, are you ready?
Good luck.
Semifinals.
This is intense.
- This is awkward.
- Who's gonna win?
They look like
they're about to throw punches.
- Good luck.
- Good luck!
Yeah.
- Gotta be quick.
- You got this.
Start the music, go!
It's getting even faster.
- I just wanna run.
- Keeping their eyes on the chairs.
- Sara, you're walking fast.
- Go for the win.
I'm stressed.
The music's so fast,
they're all so nervous.
This is so intense. I'm so nervous.
- So intense.
- The distance between us…
My God!
- Whoa!
- Come on!
Look at 'em go! They're pretty strong.
- You snatched it.
- Bad luck, Sara.
There's no rule against snatching.
Yeah, you took the chair like… Phew!
Super quick.
You're clever.
- This is insane.
- Go, Rinrin.
- I'm scared.
- Okay, final round!
- Put it in the middle.
- This round is gonna be fierce!
- I wonder who's gonna win.
- The two who've clashed.
Right, it's the two girls
who clashed from the start.
- A duel!
- It's a duel.
- The girls who clashed on day one.
- Jeez, don't remind them!
- Don't provoke them.
- Yeah, careful.
Right, here we go.
DJ?
Start the music!
Move back.
Focus.
- So intense.
- It's crazy.
Stay focused.
- Is it faster?
- It's faster.
- I'm scared.
- It's coming.
Keeping their distance.
They're both so locked in on it.
Reflexes, girls, reflexes.
- All about the reflexes.
- It's coming.
No!
Wow!
She's too strong.
- The undisputed champion.
- Good job. Well done.
- Wow, bravo. Good job.
- The undisputed champion.
That was crazy.
- I won!
- Nice one!
- Bravo!
- Well done!
Great game, girls!
It's so hot.
Well done, everybody.
The winner of the game will now choose
who she would like to go on a date with.
Please choose.
You have to say,
"I wanna go on a date with…"
Hmm…
It's gotta be him, am I right?
I haven't talked to you yet so,
Kamaken, I choose you.
Ooh!
- Have a good time.
- Thank you.
- Do your thing, have fun.
- You'll have time to talk.
- I wanna go on a date too!
- For real?
What? She chose him?
- Ryopi must be feeling…
- Yeah.
He'll be like, "What?"
- You're pretty strong.
- I have long legs.
You're too strong.
Bye-bye.
- See you.
- Bye-bye.
- Have fun.
- Let's go.
They're gonna have so much fun. Oh my.
RYUKYU GLASS WORKSHOP
GLASS HOUSE IN THE FOREST
"Glass."
- "Glass house."
- Cute.
- It is. I wanna take a photo.
- Maybe we're getting that.
- Oh, you're right.
- Oh!
That'll be it.
- Wow, look at this.
- Oh, wow.
Oh my God, this is so fun.
- It's so adorable, look at it.
- You love this kind of stuff?
I like looking at them.
They're, like, so stylish.
I smell something.
- They're super artsy.
- They're cute.
These glasses are actually nice.
- The blue one!
- These are insane.
Adorbs.
"Full of energy,
a curious and… curious and…"
- What's that say? "Curious and…"
- "Inclusive"?
That's not it.
It's "inquisitive".
Let's get something matching,
'cause we're on a date.
Like, how about a necklace
we can put on our glasses?
- That'd be nice.
- Let's try putting them together.
- Hey, that looks good.
- It's really good.
- So adorable.
- They're good.
Wow. Adorbs. Let's get these.
All righty. Okay, I'm gonna get
the big green one in one shot.
Look at this.
- Here I go.
- Go.
What?
Wow!
- You got it in!
- All right!
- That was amazing!
- This one's for you.
- No way.
- Yes way.
- Wow, thanks!
- You're welcome.
- They kind of look good together.
- I know, right?
- It's so cute.
- It's pretty.
That was amazing.
Okay, first of all,
I think it'd be a good idea for us
to think about preparations
for the welcome party.
Welcome party?
Yeah, um,
we've been doing community service,
and we probably haven't met
everyone yet, but…
Yeah, we wanna invite all
of those senior citizens who we've met,
and just throw a big welcome party
for them here.
We wanna do things for them
that they don't usually do
and make it a fun experience.
That sounds super nice.
- Hey.
- Yes?
We're gonna serve food, right?
- Yeah.
- And soon we're gonna go to a banana farm.
And we also went to the shikuwasa orchard
and the other farm.
I was thinking it might be nice
to use the food they gave us,
prepare it our own way,
and serve it to them.
- You're right. Okay, let's do that.
- Let's do that.
It's settled.
- That'd be nice.
- You spoke in sync.
- Should I make takoyaki?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Great idea.
- Like, "This is Kansai."
- Good idea. Let's go with takoyaki.
- You're both from Kansai.
- Yeah.
- Sounds good.
Hey, we should also play
some games or something.
- Like the ring toss.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- Well…
- Yeah, that would be nice.
Anything else?
Maybe at the end,
we could all write a message
on a T-shirt, you know?
- A T-shirt with messages.
- As a gift.
- Okay.
- Oh, so like a gift.
- Like a little keepsake.
- Yeah, a keepsake.
In that case, we should all have
matching T-shirts to wear on the day.
- For everyone?
- Mmm.
Okay, we'll make
matching T-shirts for everyone.
- That could work.
- And they can just wear them home.
- Yeah. That could work well.
- True.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Okay, well, how about we try making
some of these dishes,
and we see which ones work the best,
and then narrow it down?
- Mmm.
- Right.
- That should be fine.
- Mmm-hmm.
But we'll need to split up into groups.
- Yeah, I guess.
- To prepare everything.
Each of us could do our own thing.
Kazuma could do the T-shirts, for example,
- and Sara could do the Okinawa cuisine.
- Yeah.
And Ryopi or Mimi
could do the flour-based stuff.
- Okay.
- The rest of us can help out where we can.
- I wanna work on the ring toss.
- Oh, I wanna do that too.
Okay, you two do the ring toss.
- Oh! That sounds good.
- So, Tai-chan and Sharan.
- They're already coupled up.
- Yeah.
All right, let's fire it up.
Let's go!
- I wanna do it too. Let's go again.
- Come up here. We'll do it.
I'll do it here.
- All right, everyone ready?
- Yes.
- Let's…
- Go!
Why is it so funny?
THEME: FESTIVAL
RYUKYU GLASS WORKSHOP
- Wanna make one?
- Sure, let's do it.
- Yeah.
- Look at that.
- Wow, that's crazy.
- It's hot.
- I know, right?
- Look how hot it is.
So I hold it?
- Blow into it as hard as you can.
- Much harder.
- Looking good.
- A little more.
- That's it.
- Okay.
- All right.
I'm out of breath.
Look how good you did, look.
Squeeze it. Now in the middle.
- Two.
- Three.
- Okay.
- It's so cute!
All right.
- It's super cute.
- Look at that.
- It's good, right?
- It's really good!
I think it's perfect.
- How is it that cute?
- It was absolutely perfect.
This is worth making.
I feel like Rinrin's getting cuter.
Yeah, she is. They look natural together.
- They look good together.
- They do.
- Whoa.
- This is what it looks like.
- It feels, like, so nostalgic.
- Oh my God, this is amazing.
Isn't it amazing?
- Oh my God, it's so cute.
- It's insane, right?
It's actually like this?
- There are so many shisas.
- They're adorable.
- It's super stylish and cute.
- Looks delicious.
We're gonna get a mustache.
Yeah, totally!
Okay.
Enjoy your meal.
- This is lovely.
- Perfect.
- Wow, yum. Wait, I actually like it.
- Really?
Oh, this is good. Mmm.
It's kind of like chiffon cake.
You know, I actually love cooking.
- Oh, you do, do you?
- Yeah, I make bento for my little brother.
Whoa, for real?
For three years,
while I was in high school…
- Yeah.
- …I would make lunches for him.
- Are you two close?
- Super close.
- Is he a yankii?
- No, he's the opposite of me.
- Total opposite?
- He's a gamer.
He loves video games.
Mmm-hmm.
But he's the one
I really want to apologize to.
- You want to apologize?
- Yeah.
Why's that?
We grew up in a single-parent household
with my mom.
So my brother and I had to stay home alone
while Mom was at work.
Right.
And we used
to get into fights pretty often.
I used to pin him down really hard
so he couldn't move.
I mean, so he wouldn't move.
And I'd slap him a lot.
- Your little brother?
- Yeah.
- I see.
- He never listened, so…
Siblings fight.
- Right.
- Uh-huh.
- And I really kind of…
- Hmm.
I mean, looking back,
a part of me feels like I went too far.
- Mmm-hmm.
- But I've never apologized to him.
- Okay. Yeah.
- So I really want to apologize.
I guess making his lunches all those years
was my way of repaying…
- Not "repaying," but…
- I get what you mean.
It was just my way
of showing that I felt bad.
- Uh-huh.
- So I tried to show him that way.
But I just haven't been able to say it.
So, yeah, I want to apologize.
That's good of you.
We have a nine-year age gap
between us, don't we?
- We do.
- Yeah.
- Or it might be closer to ten, you know?
- Thought so.
Be honest, how do you feel about that?
Like, the age difference.
It's kind of weird, I don't know why,
but all my exes…
- Yeah?
- …have been older.
- Like six years older.
- Really?
Yeah.
Like, guys who are my age,
or guys around my age,
just seem childish to me.
- Right.
- I can't deal with them.
I just don't see them as romantic options.
- Oh, okay.
- And the reason I asked you out today is…
- Yeah? I'm really curious why.
- Yeah. Like…
I couldn't tell
what your personality was like,
but looks-wise, I thought
you were definitely the best-looking.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- You're kidding.
- I'm not.
- Because…
- The others are good-looking, though.
- Can I be honest?
- Hmm.
I just really don't like having to hide
how I feel or not being honest.
- Mmm-hmm.
- In the past,
I found it really hard
to be honest with myself.
- Hmm.
- …and I ended up having to pay the price.
I don't want that to happen again,
so I've decided to be honest this time.
Yeah. I think that's good.
I think a lot of women tend to hold back
from saying what they really think.
- More than men do.
- I guess so.
Like, guys,
if something bothers us, we speak up.
- Hmm.
- Like yesterday, with Kazuma.
But it seems like
a lot of girls don't do that.
Yeah, that's true.
But you're different, you actually do.
What I'm trying to say is you have guts,
and you know who you are.
Honestly, I think…
…that's pretty cool.
- You not thirsty?
- Hmm.
- You didn't like it?
- It's not that.
- Not in the mood?
- I'm just nervous.
- Why?
- I'm not good at this stuff.
You're nervous?
- No way.
- When I'm alone with someone…
Yeah?
…my personality changes a little.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
- That side of you is cute.
- That's not what I meant.
No, but I just mean that
I think it's cute when someone
who's usually real tough gets all shy.
I didn't expect it to go like that.
I thought if I talked to him,
I'd still be like, "Ryopi's the one."
Yeah, like…
Look what's become of me.
I'm so easily won over.
"Look what's become of me." What a phrase.
- Like an enka ballad.
- You'd only hear that in enka.
"Look what's become of me."
"I'm so easily won over."
"I've become one of those women."
I mean, Ryopi is a really nice guy too.
Kamaken is just way more straightforward,
but, I mean, he also knows
how to pay her a compliment.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- He gives off that mature-guy vibe.
- Yeah, exactly.
- True.
- He's reliable.
So where do you think Ryopi stands now?
There was a subtle look on his face
earlier, when she didn't pick him.
He was wearing sunglasses,
but you could still tell.
But who knows what Ryopi thinks?
Because Rinrin keeps coming at him.
- He might wanna talk to other girls more.
- That's true.
So maybe he's actually
just resetting himself.
- That's possible.
- Yeah, that's a possibility.
I wonder if he's interested
in anybody else.
LOVE
Sharan,
your face was bright red yesterday.
Yeah, I was drunk.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
- You mean, when I said, "Gross"?
- Yeah, that.
Mmm.
You were bad-mouthing Mimi.
- I wasn't bad-mouthing her--
- You were like, "She's so annoying."
- Fine, I won't say it again, okay?
- What do you mean?
No. Just forget it.
Yeah, I guess that's the part
that's been bothering me.
I'm sorry for, like, complaining so much.
Yeah. Part of me was like,
"Why is she telling me?"
- I'm really sorry about that.
- Mmm.
Yeah. I think I've just…
I just always screw up when it comes
to these types of situations.
- Right.
- Up until now.
Hmm.
People always say,
"Why are you angry over that?"
Or "I just don't get it."
Or "You're so annoying."
And I thought about all those times,
and like, that's it.
I just get jealous of pretty girls.
- Yeah, you said that before.
- I mean, Mimi is cute.
- Hmm.
- Hey, cute.
- That was cute just now.
- Yeah.
What about you?
How do you feel about Mimi?
- Hmm, I think I'd like to talk to her.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I'd like to.
You said you wanted
to do the same, remember?
- So I should be able to do that too.
- Okay, well, then I'm done.
- What?
- I don't care anymore.
What do you mean, you don't care?
Look, I guess it's okay if you get jealous
in this environment.
Mmm.
But everybody in here
is trying to get to know each other
on a serious level,
- so you can't put that all on me.
- Mmm.
So when you complain to me
like you did at the beach,
there's nothing I can really do about it.
- Mmm.
I want to get to know everybody too,
especially the girls I'm interested in.
- Mmm. Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Makes sense.
You had a lot to say
about the fact that I was spending
one-on-one time with Mimi.
- Do you remember?
- Mmm.
It made me wonder,
what if it were the other way around?
Like when you asked Rune out on a date,
I wonder how you would've felt
if you were in my shoes.
I worked hard and came first,
so I thought
I was the one who deserved the date.
And even though you chose Rune,
I was frustrated, sure,
but it didn't turn into anger
or anything beyond that.
So, I wonder how you'd feel
if you were in my shoes,
and I still snapped at you afterwards.
Hmm, yeah.
- He's right.
- Yeah.
So Tai-chan actually was hurt by that.
Do you feel like you want to change?
- I did, but now, I don't even know.
- Mmm.
Okay.
I feel like whatever happens, happens.
I just feel so lost now.
I'm like, whatever.
Hmm.
So…
Let's have a smoke.
- Looks so good.
- Add that.
They'll be crispy outside
and fluffy inside.
- Really?
- Yep.
- It's hot, so eat it in one.
- Can I use this?
One bite.
- One bite?
- Yeah.
- That's crazy.
- In one bite. Not yet.
- This is dangerous.
- Why?
It's scalding hot.
- Don't worry, it's not hot.
- Really? Sure?
Real men are supposed
to eat takoyaki in one bite.
- Okay, I got this, Mimi.
- Don't you dare spit it out.
- I got this. Are you sure about this?
- Yep.
- Go. Now.
- For real?
- Don't cool it down, just do it.
- You guys are lying.
Be a man.
Ow, hot!
Hot, hot, hot! It's too hot!
- This is not okay.
- It's pretty hot, huh?
I really don't think
I can handle another week of this.
Hmm.
I'm being way too emotionally unstable,
I'm, like, totally grossing myself out.
Hmm.
But if you realize that about yourself,
I think that could be a real opportunity
for you to change.
But if you don't even realize it,
then you can't change.
Yeah.
- Who are you interested in?
- Seriously?
Well, if you ask me
who I'm interested in or want to talk to…
I guess it's Mimi,
because we haven't had many chances
to talk yet.
- That's how I feel.
- Mmm-hmm.
Fine, whatever.
What's wrong? Come on, let's go inside.
- I'm done.
- Is it Tai-chan?
He said he was interested in Mimi.
What was everything up until now?
I don't know. I'm, like, "Whatever."
- I don't understand Tai-chan anymore.
- Hmm.
I have feelings for Tai-chan, so, yeah…
I guess it just really hurts.
I started liking him in a romantic way,
I got too aggressive and pushed too hard,
and now I've just screwed it all up.
I'm not sure
I'm capable of a relationship.
I've even started thinking
about dropping out.
That's how much I've given up.
I really want to fix this issue I have.
But I've only got one week left in here.
People are always gonna want
what they can't have, know what I mean?
That's exactly what's happening here.
I want them to click
a little bit better now.
But now Sharan's saying
that she wants to drop out of school.
Yeah, I'm getting worried about her.
She's, like, starting to get
a little emotionally unstable.
Right.
If someone could step in to support her,
that might help her.
Tai-chan was grilling her hard,
which was unusual for him.
It was, yeah. It all goes back
to the race where he carried her.
Just when Tai-chan thought
he won the chance to go on a date,
Sharan chose Rune.
That's where it fell apart
for Tai-chan too.
Exactly.
I feel like with the students
from group two…
- Yeah?
- …we can finally sit back.
The dating show
has finally begun, thank you.
- How many times have we said that?
- I have to keep saying it.
- Or it won't start?
- Or it won't start.
- Got it.
- It's a warning,
even though I'm saying "thank you."
You know those signs, "Thank you
for keeping this restroom clean"?
- Right, right.
- I see.
Same idea.
So thank you to all the crew members.
Now we can finally watch
an actual reality dating show
- with the group two students.
- Look at that!
- Look how he's bowing to you.
- Much appreciated.
Man.
- Oh, there they are!
- I really love these two.
I wanted to go on that date so badly.
- You really mean that?
- Yeah. Sure.
What? I wanted to.
Really?
Well, my mind is pretty much
made up already.
What do you mean by "pretty much"?
Is it between two people,
or are you like 90% sure on one guy?
- Uh-huh.
- Well? Which one?
- 90%
- Oh, the latter.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I see.
Who would you have picked today?
- What do you mean?
- If you'd won the game.
Well, I would've picked you.
- Whoa!
- Okay!
- She said it.
- What?
Why are you smirking like that?
- I didn't do anything. Huh?
- I thought you were cute.
- You're cute.
- Oh. Thanks.
Of course.
I thought she'd tell it to him
straight today, but I guess not.
Exactly.
- It feels more true this way.
- It does.
If she said it every time,
it'd feel forced.
Right.
- Sara, can we talk?
- Sure.
I was thinking I wanted to give you
my drawing sometime before graduation.
- Okay.
- Just for you.
- Seriously?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- But I can't draw portraits or anything.
- Okay.
I haven't done much sketching,
but I'm studying
Japanese-style designs right now.
So, I wanna design
a traditional Japanese back tattoo.
I mean, I draw that kind of thing
all the time anyway,
so I wanted to give you one as a gift.
I've never been given
a gift like that before, like, ever.
- Oh, yeah?
- Never. Nobody does that.
I think it's really sweet.
Wow, this is crazy, I'm excited.
It's something more to look forward to.
- Should we eat?
- Yeah.
- Okay, hands together.
- Okay.
- Let's eat!
Let's eat.
Mmm, yum!
- This is so good.
- Mmm.
How's it going?
- We made good progress.
- Yeah?
- We made a lot of food.
- The takoyaki is tasting great.
Yeah, the takoyaki was amazing.
- Should be good.
- I know, right?
So good.
- We're back.
- Hey, welcome back.
- Hey.
- Hey, you want some dinner?
- Not for you.
- Did you eat?
- We did.
But seeing as you made it,
I'll have a bite.
- Me too.
- Don't do that.
If you're going to half-ass it,
don't bother.
- Huh?
- Oh.
- That had a bit of an edge to it.
- Yeah.
- Tell us about your date.
- For sure.
- Why are you grinning like that?
No, I… I don't know.
I'm so jealous.
Was it the first time you spent alone?
- Yeah.
- We hadn't had a proper conversation.
- That's nice for your first date.
- Sounds awesome.
- I was nervous.
- It was.
And the cafe was deep in the mountains.
- It had a second floor, but it was quiet.
- Yeah.
Not a single sound.
- Oh, I see.
- So, yeah.
What's with you two
not making eye contact? Like…
They're not, are they?
- No! What are you talking about?
- Nothing to tell.
- It didn't go well, they're like…
- Can I take a photo of you two?
A post-date shot.
Show us how close you feel.
Pose like you like each other.
What does that mean?
No, perfect.
Show us how close you two are.
- No, our heads didn't touch.
- Say, "Cheese."
- Is this a one-sided crush?
- A one-sided crush?
How's that?
- So the date…
- Tell us.
Anyway, we went and did this glass thing.
- What's it called?
- The glasses?
- We made glasses.
- Ryukyu glass?
- That's it.
- I love Ryukyu glass.
- It was dragon-like.
- Wow.
- You blow air into it and shape it.
- Oh, I know!
So we made glasses and bought
these little phone charms too.
- Wow.
- For everyone?
- No, for us two.
- Oh.
"For everyone?" Seriously?
- Would've been nice.
- Didn't bring us souvenirs?
You guys could only think
about yourselves, huh? Whatever.
He's like, "For everyone?"
- Ow, that's hot.
- Was it fun?
Yeah, after that…
- Mimi isn't joining in the conversation?
- What does this mean?
So, Rinrin, how was the date?
I'm curious.
Who, me?
I mean, I… I had a good time.
Um, I don't know how to say it.
I felt like I could…
finally relax after a long time.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I felt really refreshed.
Mmm.
I got to hear a lot about Kamaken's story,
and he listened to my story as well.
I guess I'm glad I asked him out.
Mmm.
- How do you feel?
- How do I feel?
- I'm interested in him.
- I see.
- Hmm.
- Mimi, how do you feel about it?
- Huh?
- Hmm?
- Wow, that was sudden.
- No, we're going around the circle.
You're being unusually quiet.
No, it's just… seeing them
come back, grinning like that,
got on my nerves a little bit.
- Like, "Kamaken's all happy now."
- He was grinning.
- He said he was interested in you.
- No, I mean…
He's also a transfer student like me,
I'm sure that's part of why he's curious.
- But I don't think he does casual.
- Yeah, that's true.
I guess it depends on who else
notices me and what I do from here.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
MEN
Kamaken, how was the date?
Yeah. You talked a lot.
- Well, today…
- Mmm.
…we had a lot of fun,
kind of like we were kids, you know?
- I see.
- We really had a good time.
And did your impression of her change?
- It did change a bit, yeah.
- Oh, yeah?
I used to think she was intimidating,
like really bold and full-on.
I get that.
But I got to see
a different side of her today.
- Oh, wow.
- So I see her a little differently now.
Yeah.
So, do you think that it could lead
to romantic feelings, or…
Hmm, well, I mean,
if it has to be either yes or no,
I'd say I'm leaning toward a yes.
Ohhh!
That must have been
super tough for him to have to hear.
Yeah.
BADLY IN LOVE
MARINE ACADEMY
Morning.
Good morning.
- Are we sitting all spread out again?
- Morning.
Have a seat.
- What's up?
- Hey, Rune.
- You look cute today too.
What?
Spread out.
Oh, no.
- I actually drew you, Mimi.
- I heard the drawing was of a guy.
I drew that.
- Right?
- Right.
Damn, I feel bad for her.
I know.
Good morning, students.
Morning.
We have
two important announcements to make today.
- What is it?
- I'm scared.
- For tomorrow…
- Huh?
…we've planned
an overnight date for two of you.
Wait, for who?
Tomorrow, there will be a contest.
Whichever guy wins the contest
will be the one who gets to choose a woman
to go on the overnight date with.
- Got it.
- I'm definitely going to win this.
Huh? What?
- Wait…
- What's this?
Hey…
- Who's she?
- Who is this?
- An overnight date!
- That's crazy.
Where are we going?
- It sounds good.
- All of us?
- No way. Definitely not.
It's a date.
The guys have to compete for it.
- Oh.
- I wanna go.
Wanna go?
The other announcement is…
- Yeah, I think so.
- Well…
- Overnight…
- Wait, wait, wait.
Huh?
- What?
- Who's that?
- Hello.
- Hey.
- You surprised me.
- What the hell?
I'm Kaho Chinen, the transfer student.
- No way!
- Huh? Now? Out of nowhere?
- That's crazy.
- For real? Holy cow.
- Crazy.
- A transfer student now?
- Nice to meet you all.
- So sudden.
- Get her to introduce herself.
- Okay.
- I'm from Okinawa.
- Really?
- No way!
- Same as you.
- Really?
- Oh, she's from Okinawa.
- Damn.
- Let's introduce ourselves.
- I'd like that.
- This way around?
- To remind ourselves.
- You be the MC.
- We have an MC.
- Okay, I'll do it. So…
Can I just step outside for a second?
I can't…
- What?
- What happened?
- Sharan?
- What'd I do this time?
"What'd I do this time?" Nothing.
You did nothing.
- What's wrong?
- I'm pissed.
- And so…
- No way!
We now have another new transfer student.
This late in the game?
She has joined us
right at the very end of the second half.
Okay, with her,
the head count is now finally…
- Right.
- Six and six? It's even.
- It's even, yeah.
- Oh, right.
- Where is this going?
- Exactly.
And that overnight date too.
Man, I'm so curious about that.
The first group was crazy.
- I know, right?
- It was intense.
- We were like… like this.
- Really?
- Yeah, it was so intense.
- It was erotic. Super erotic.
"Super erotic"?
What kind of stupid comment is that?
- Be serious.
- Badly in Lust.
- Not Badly in Lust, for God's sake.